What's wrong?
Can't sleep?
You get lonely because you're cold.
Wakana, you're sleeping sideways again.
I Want to End This Love Game
Episode 6
My Childhood Friend Wants to Sleep Over
Nice shot!
Good try!
So hot...
PE class with the outgoing kids is a pain.
Look at you, freaking out.
It's hot today, huh?
Here you go.
Did I give off manager vibes?
Get your heart racing?
Managers do more than
just hand over drinks.
The gym was so hot.
It's about time we get AC, huh?
No kidding.
You're drenched in sweat.
You're going to catch a cold.
I'll wipe...
Wipe yourself down.
You smell like sweat.
I won't do anything that you'd hate.
Maybe it's just me, but he hasn't
been as aggressive ever since that day.
Girls' Locker Room
m 425.001 324.999 l 425.001 729.999 1488 729.999 1488 324.999
What does he think he's doing?
Does he think he needs to go easy on me?
Yukiya doesn't deserve
to look down on me like that.
Cooling Wipes
He doesn't need to be careful.
He could just come at me.
You smell like sweat.
Wait, hang on...
Is that it?
Is that really it?
Is it not that he's being careful
or courteous or anything...
Is it because I'm still not
enough of a girl for him?
Huh? I think you're really cute, though.
Onii probably is interested
in you, I think...
H-He is, right?
Do you think so?
He'll never admit it, though.
This sucks.
This is just a hunch, but...
Onii was looking at this scene
in a game the other day...
I'll put you in full bloom!
“Cosmo Connect”                            Special Moves Compilation
200,000 views               1 month ago          #cosmoconnect
He was like...
These are huge.
...as he was watching.
Princess Floral!
I-Is that why?
Is it because I'm flat?
He said something about
her having crazy high DPS.
m 204 86.376 l 657 86.376 657 240 204 240
High DPS:
In a video game, this refers
to having high damage output.
What's DPS?
Is it because I don't
pack any hopes or dreams?
Are you serious?!
I can't stand guys!
Maybe now's the time to see what
advice shoujo manga can offer.
Huh? But manga isn't reality.
You don't get it, Miku-chan.
You see, shoujo manga
has a 50-year history,
Blah, blah~
a lot of it focused on love.
It depicts countless
romantic situations,
so there's no way none
of them apply to you.
So Yukiya was using
shoujo manga as a reference
Blah, blah~
She acts just like
a mini-Yukiya!
Surely there's something
you can learn from it.
because of Wakana-chan's influence.
And based on my research,
97% of shoujo manga protagonists
end up getting together.
O-Okay.
True, most stories
end that way...
Point is, you can be successful
if you follow shoujo manga, too.
Well, hm...
I guess.
You may have a point.
Yup, yup.
Be mine.
Huh...
Your tie's
crooked.
Huh?
I made you lunch!
Hang on...
We're right out of a shoujo manga, no?
Why? Why?
Why isn't it working out?
Okay.
I need to be more assertive.
Maybe there's something in here.
Something more...
That's it!
I haven't done this one yet!
This is it!
I guess this is our first
night alone together.
Yeah.
Your blanket has your scent.
It's so relaxing.
Oh, but you're going to catch a cold.
I'll wrap you up.
Miku...
You win.
I've been stubborn this whole time, but...
What if...
My parents...
aren't home
today.
Do you want to
sleep over?
But how?
Do I have to ask him
to let me stay over?
Stay over?
At my place?
You sure you aren't just
using gaming as an excuse
to do that kind of stuff with me?
What a tramp.
No!
No, no, no!
I'm putting my body on the line
because you won't get turned on by me!
I'm not hoping for that
kind of thing to begin with!
But if we could...
If we could just hang out
normally, that'd be nice.
Like we used to.
How long has it been
since I've been over?
Thanks for being her friend
going forward, Yukiya-kun.
Oh, Miku-chan. Morning.
Come in.
Let's play video games together.
I Want to End This Love Game
Miku-chan, do you want seconds?
Um...
I'm okay.
Yeah?
You don't need to hold back, okay?
Mom, more.
And some furikake.
You need to start
getting some for yourself.
Onii, the soy sauce!
I forgot to ask if I can
use the hair dryer.
Oh hey, Sakura!
Bones'
Friend
Milk
Beverage
Cocoa
Here.
I've been making some
while Mom's not watching.
Bones'
Friend
Milk
Beverage
Cocoa
Hurry up. Before she catches us.
Thanks.
It's sweet.
And crunchy.
I added extra powder for you.
Don't worry about it.
Just this once, since
you seemed down, Sakura.
Bones'
Friend
Milk
Beverage
Cocoa
Hey...
Can I borrow the hair dryer?
Yay! I won!
Once more, Miku!
I'm going to play for real this time.
Sure.
One more time.
Thank you so much.
Miku, I can stay home
all the time starting tomorrow.
Really?!
Do you want to keep
playing our game tomorrow?
I wanna play!
Mom, can I?
Of course.
I'm glad you made a good friend.
I love you!
“We Tried Playing the I Love You Game”
I love you, Yukiya.
Wait a second...
I think it goes like this.
Oh, right.
Yukiya.
Hey...
Can we study again?
N-Never mind. Sorry.
Nacchan, Nacchan!
Wanna study at your place today?
Waka
Wakana-chan. What's up?
Hey, hear me out, Miku-chan!
Mom and Dad are gone for
their friends' wedding, and...
I'm home.
Wakana, I know you wanted
kimchi hot pot today,
but they didn't have chives...
Welcome home, honey.
Would you like dinner?
Would you like a bath?
Or maybe...
League battle?
Uh-oh, what's wrong?
A little petrified?
Were you excited that
I might say something else?
W-Wait, wait, wait!
Why an a-apron?
Actually, why are you even here?
Wakana-chan called.
She said your mom and dad are staying
the night in Shikoku for a wedding.
So, what'll it be?
Dinner? A bath? League battle?
Dinner.
Okay!
I'll make enough for tomorrow, too.
Th-That wasn't weird, was it?
He didn't notice me getting timid, did he?
I'm just here to make dinner.
I'm just here to make dinner today.
One hour ago
Welcome. Come in.
Th-Thanks for having me.
It hasn't changed at all.
It still smells like Yukiya's place.
Wasn't the sofa bigger?
Today's the day I
knock him into this sofa!
He's having a cute
girl cook at his place.
No boy could ever resist that, right?
m 105 810.999 l 105 998.001 615.999 998.001 615.999 810.999
Victory Apron
I'm gonna go all-out and
knock-him out once and for all.
Do you see how attractive I am now?
No...
It isn't just a matter of seducing him.
I'm going to get Yukiya
to tell me I'm cute.
Miku's cooking for us at my place?
Holy crap, this is too awesome!
It's the same Miku in front of me,
yet she's nothing like she was.
There it is.
Just the thought that Miku's here
where I always spend my time...
Wh-What?
Why're you just standing there?
Let me guess...
Seeing me in my apron
is just too much for you?
That little...
No wonder she decided
to barge in. I knew it!
What?
That's supposed to be an apron?
I thought it was a giant baby bib.
Anyway, what are you making?
Beef and potato stew.
Wow.
Then, for dessert, I'll have you.
Then, for dessert...
What are you doing with those hands?
Oh, right.
You haven't had your welcome home hug.
Sure. Let's hug.
I-I haven't washed my hands yet.
I don't want Wakana getting sick.
Wait a minute...
I'm pretty sure this is working!
Oh yeah, Yukiya...
I remember you like your stew sweet.
Could you try tasting it?
O-Okay.
Oh, wait.
Hm? What's wrong?
It's okay now.
What's wrong? Are you feeling shy?
Or do you want me
to blow on it some more?
Stop it. You're going to
get your spit in it.
I guess it's on the better side.
Right? It's pretty good, right?
This was my absolute favorite flavor.
I knew it.
I got him good!
Of course.
Of course!
Are you sure?
Don't cut your fingers.
Make a cat paw with your left hand, okay?
You say that like I'm stupid.
I know how to use a knife.
Oh, wow.
You're doing diagonal cuts.
Is it because you're always so salty
that you know how to cook?
In fact, I've been
making miso soup lately.
You? Really?
Make me some, then!
Fool. Don't expect any soup for you.
We haven't even started eating and
it's so sweet I'm getting heartburn.
Wow! You're always such a good cook!
Yukiya did help out.
Well, I'll be heading home now.
Huh? Aren't you going to eat with us?
Nah, I just came to cook.
I'll eat at home.
Stay for dinner.
I mean, you'll get lonely having
dinner with just me, right?
Exactly.
Onii looks lonely, too.
You haven't been here
in such a long time.
You should make yourself
at home, if you don't mind.
Okay...
I guess I wouldn't mind, if you insist.
I'll let Mom know, though.
Huh?
Mom
Today
Missed Call
Mom?
Miku?
Thank goodness. Are you all right?
Huh?
I went home to get something earlier,
and the door was unlocked
and no one was home.
Sorry! I left in such a hurry...
She came here in a hurry?
Hey...
Sorry about today.
Like, I've never seen you
cooking like a grown-up before.
It took me by surprise.
Wakana seemed happy, too.
Plus it was pretty helpful overall.
Thanks.
Thanks for walking me home.
Good night.
What's wrong?
Er...
I left home in a hurry, and...
I think I left my keys inside.
Mom locked the door
on her way to her night shift.
Th-Then...
Wanna stay over?
'Kay.
Next Time
My Childhood Friend Wants to Win
Okay...
If Onii ends up taking it too far,
we're going to change the title from
"I Want to End This Love Game," right?
Next episode: "My Childhood
Friend Wants to Win."